A Guide to the Director of the Virginia Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation Correspondence and Subject files, 1970-2022
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Directors correspondence and subject files [Acc. 34743],., Extent: 50 cu. ft. (50 boxes). (Box 1-)
  - Board of Geology, 1981-1985 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Board of Hearing Aid Dealers and Fitters, 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - State Board for the Certification of Librarians, 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Private Security Services and Businesses Regulations, 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 12-13)
  - State Board of Opticians, 1979-1987 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Board of Commissioners to Examine Pilots, 1983-1986 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Real Estate Board, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Real Estate Board, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Real Estate Board, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1986 December (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1986 December-1987 January (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1988 January-March (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1988 March-May (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1988 May-June (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1988 June-August (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1988 August (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1988 August-October (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1988 October-December (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1990 January (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1990 January-April (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1989 May (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1989 June (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1989 July (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1989 August (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Sec. of Economic Development, Richard M. Bagley, Correspondence, 1986 September-1987 January (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Policy Analyst, Catherine M. Walker, Correspondence, 1986 April-1987 April (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Deputy Director for Financial Management, Theresa A. Palmer, Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Dept. of Commerce, Director's Office, Correspondence, 1986 January-December (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate Board, 1987 June 16-17 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Board, 1987 July 22 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Real Estate Board, 1987 August 4 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Accountancy, State Board, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Accountancy, State Board, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Accountancy, Regulations, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Accountancy, Proposed regulations, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Accountancy, Self Audit, Section 1, 1984-1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Accountancy, Self Audit, Section 2, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - APELSCLA, Regulations, Section A, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - APELSCLA, Regulations, Section B, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - APELSCLA, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - APELSCLA, Self Audit, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - APELSCLA, Attorney General, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Asbestos, Contractors, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Board, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Auctioneers, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Auctioneers, Proposed legislation, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Audiology/Speech, 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Barbers, 1982-1987 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Certified landscape architect, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Board of Commerce, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Contractors, State Board, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Contractors, Proposed legislation, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Contractor Transaction Recovery Act Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Cosmetology, Board, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Cosmetology, Board, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Driver training, 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Employment agencies, 1985-1987 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - (Box 31)